{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050467417","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050467417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 38a3515a-468f-4c0e-a221-844b098cce79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_b_m"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050473247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050473247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 38a3515a-468f-4c0e-a221-844b098cce79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_j_b_m"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050483402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050483401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 1c86d90a-dfc4-4532-ab42-3fac98b6fb69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050483635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050483635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 1c86d90a-dfc4-4532-ab42-3fac98b6fb69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050484608","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050484607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 1c86d90a-dfc4-4532-ab42-3fac98b6fb69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050485881","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050485881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 1c86d90a-dfc4-4532-ab42-3fac98b6fb69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050488469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050488469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 1c86d90a-dfc4-4532-ab42-3fac98b6fb69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050488546","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050488546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 1c86d90a-dfc4-4532-ab42-3fac98b6fb69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050508562","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050508561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050522148","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050522148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050531752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050531752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050556975","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050556975"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050565288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050565288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050575017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050575016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050576915","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050576915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050590649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050590649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050603952","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050603952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050614752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050614752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_f"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050624527","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050624527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050635293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050635293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050646353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050646352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050658674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050658674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050669493","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050669493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050678898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050678898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050689175","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050689175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050699639","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050699639"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_l"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050710005","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050710005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050719923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050719923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050729386","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050729386"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_o"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050744206","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050744206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050754458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050754458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050762304","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050762304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050773583","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050773583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050783099","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050783099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050786931","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050786931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 72c5e08b-97f7-4c6a-a54a-c417e7a18e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050794034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050794034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 803bae88-3a52-49f3-870f-9cb241def75b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050816869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050816868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 803bae88-3a52-49f3-870f-9cb241def75b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050819604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050819603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 803bae88-3a52-49f3-870f-9cb241def75b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050819730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050819730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" 803bae88-3a52-49f3-870f-9cb241def75b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050833066","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050833066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_h-r-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050836409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050836408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_w-y-j"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050840135","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050840135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_y-i-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050843752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050843752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_l-k-j"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050847352","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050847351"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-y-w"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050850916","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050850915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_y-m-i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050854652","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050854651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-n-k"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050858491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050858491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_j-l-p"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050862321","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050862321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-m-f"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050866409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050866409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-p-v"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050872589","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050872589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-p-v"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050876882","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050876882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_o-b-l"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050880789","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050880789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-v-e"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050884389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050884388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_s-v-k"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050888254","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050888254"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_g-a-d"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050893199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050893199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_p-z-d"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050896765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050896765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-k-z"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050900475","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050900475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_t-i-n"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050904872","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050904872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_v-h-l"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050909148","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050909148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-y-h"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050912638","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050912637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-j-z"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050919631","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050919630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-l"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050925373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050925373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-o-y"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050928819","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050928819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_s-m-r"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050932713","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050932713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_n-a-u"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050938449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050938449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_a_n-a-u"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050946968","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050946968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_n-a-u"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549050958414","data":{"timestamp":" 1549050958413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_224717"," gameId":" e46bfed9-d7f8-4d4b-aed4-30b55361e651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_n-a-u"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}